Finding aid for the J. Paul Getty Art and Real Estate Holding Companies Records, 1939, 1960-1982 and undated IA20011
Institutional Records and Archives
- Gaiola Corporation and Italian properties, 1966-1980; undated; Series III.; 5.4 Linear Feet (9 boxes)
  - Photographs, 1970-1980; Subseries III.C.; 1 Linear Feet (1 box and 1 flat file)
    Records consist of undated photographs of the houses at, and an undated map of, Gaiola, the island off the coast of Naples purchased by J. Paul Getty through the Gaiola Corporation. The black and white photographs illustrate the condition of the house; many are number coded to correspond to the floor plan of the house. Others have typed notations (in Italian) describing the view. The color photographs were originally found in the financial information records, but moved to this subseries because they did not seem to correspond to the records in which they were originally found. They depict various views of the Gaiola property.
    - Photographs, undated (Box 1986.IA.13-8, Folder loose in box)
      [Plan of house with key to photographs rehoused into Flat File 1.]
    - Plan of Gaiola house, undated (Box 1986.IA.13-09, Folder Flat file 1)